Wash It
All Away
Episode 9   Power's Out
Kinme Cleaning
Watch Out for Fall Mold
We're seeing a lot of
mold damage due to
the lack of sunny
days this year!
Mold starts to grow
when the temperature
is between 20-30°C
and humidity is around 70%.
We recommend leaving
your closet doors open
before you go out!!
We are happy to clean
your moldy clothes
for you here.
Relaxing
One-Day
Trip
Girls' Trip to the Elegant
Resort on Hatsushima
The resort's large seaside pool is only open in the summer and
allows you to enjoy a spectacular view of the ocean while you relax!
While Hatsushima has no sandy beaches, the pool is fun for
the family and a safe way to swim while taking in the ocean.
The pool actually uses seawater.
Look for the big cherry tree!
...this is
the business
she owns.
In addition to
clothes, we also
clean bags, hats,
plush toys, and...
The rain is getting heavier.
The news did say that it will get
even worse this evening and overnight.
Maybe I should give up
on visiting the bath today.
Store Receipt
Customer
Ishimochi Kashimi
sama
Ready on
Kinme
He still hasn't come to pick it up.
And there's only two days
left of summer vacation.
It probably just slipped his mind.
You two are absolutely soaked!
Sorry, Kinme-san.
Is it okay if we take cover in here?
Of course! Go right ahead.
So like, we were doing homework
at the library and when we left,
it totally started pouring.
You probably shouldn't be
out and about today anyway.
I'm working on a stain right now,
so I'd better get back to it.
Feel free to stay a while and dry off.
All right!
Yeah. Thanks.
Kinme-san always seems so busy.
The resort's large
seaside pool is only open in the
summer and allows you to
enjoy a spectacular view of
the ocean while you relax!
While Hatsushima has no
sandy beaches, the pool is
fun for the family and a
safe way to swim while taking
in the ocean.
The pool actually uses seawater.
Whoa! What the heck? It's Kinme-san!
Oh, Hatsushima?
I'm so jealous! Did you go for fun?
Man, this takes me back. We went there
for an elementary school field trip!
Yeah, I remember that.
Um, I didn't exactly go for fun.
During our field trip there,
when we were all fishing on the seawall...
Whoa!
Kyu-kun caught a stingray
and everyone went nuts!
It's a stingray!
A stingray!
Yay! Yay!
Moruda decided to try
to mess with it and, like,
he almost got stung!
Yeah, I remember that. Stingray tails
have those nasty venomous barbs.
Huh, what a fun memory.
Uh-huh. So was this your first trip
to Hatsushima, Kinme-san?
Yes, probably.
Hmm? Oh!
Thanks for the towel, Kinme-san.
Huh?
The rain lightened up some,
so I'd better run home.
Oh? There's really no need to rush.
Actually, it's my turn
to cook dinner tonight.
You can stay longer if you want, Kyu-kun.
M'kay, see you next term!
Oh, she's gone.
Well, I should probably get going too.
Wait just a minute, Kyusho-kun.
I'll get your bag for you.
Oh, that's right.
I totally forgot about it.
I thought so. Wait right there.
I should be done with the stain soon.
So she does have a good memory.
The pool actually
uses seawater.
Power's out.
Wait, weren't you just
running the washer and dryer?
Yes, they both stopped mid-course.
Huh?
What are you gonna do?
Isn't that bad for the clothes?
I'm not going to do a thing.
Huh?
In a situation like this,
panicking and pulling out everything
being washed and dried
would probably be riskier for the clothes.
I'll wait and see, and once the power is
back, maybe just start everything over.
Makes sense.
But the question is, how long is
the power going to stay out for?
It would be great if it came back
before I have to close shop.
Oh! I was going to give you
your bag. I'll go get it.
Here you go.
Thanks.
P-Please take good care of it, okay?
Uh, sure.
Oh, here. I should lend you an umbrella.
Actually...
Huh?
Maybe I'll stay a little longer.
Yeah, I mean, you don't
seem to like it much.
Thunder.
It doesn't bother me at all!
I-If it doesn't last... very long.
Yeah. Bullseye.
B-But it isn't as scary
as ghosts, at least!
Huh? She's scared of ghosts too?
The rain's getting heavier again.
Th-Then maybe you should
stay a little longer.
We are closed for the day.
Hmm. Power still isn't back yet,
and it's already starting to get dark.
Message
Power go
out there?
Mom
It's already
back here
Do you need me home soon?
Sounds like this is the only area
where power is still out.
Power go
out there?
It's already
back here
Do you need me home soon?
Mom
I'll be fine!
Looks like Mom can handle
the inn by herself.
She can?
Whoa! That's close!
Huh? What? What is that sound?
That lightning strike might have
knocked something over in the back.
Huh?
I'll go check the back entrance!
Yeah...
Thanks for lending me something to wear.
Not at all.
Those are the only things
I had here in your size.
I bought that track jacket
to practice cleaning stains on.
This is totally fine with me.
Thanks a lot.
I can't offer much, but why
don't you eat before you go?
Huh?
Thanks, but I really don't want to impose.
Oh, it's no trouble at all.
Think of it as thanks for putting
the washing machine back upright.
Wash It All Away
I really do appreciate the help.
Thank you so much.
There's nothing I could've
done about it by myself.
Sure.
Yum! This dried fish...
It tastes the same as the fish
we serve guests at the inn.
Yes, isn't it good?
It's from that store by the beach,
Gift Shop
Atsuei Dried Fish Shop
the Atsuei Dried Fish Shop.
The Atsuei Dried Fish Shop.
The first time I tasted it,
I was so impressed.
Here you go, honey. Enjoy.
What? But I'm still
on the clock right now.
Mmm!
She wears glasses.
Mom
They say the
warnings are active
until sunrise
Mom
What about your dinner
Message
Mom
Edit
They say the
warnings are
active until sunrise
What about your dinner
Kinme-san made
me dinner
Mom
I'll call
Huh? Call?
Hello?
Yeah.
Yeah, we're fine.
And over there?
Well, that's good.
Huh? You want me to put Kinme-san on?
Mom says she wants to talk.
Huh? To me?
Hello, Ishimochi-san? Good evening.
Uh... No, it's no trouble.
No, not at all. In fact,
I should be the one apologizing.
Huh? Oh, I see.
I'm real sorry about this, Kinme-san.
I can drive over and pick Kyu up.
It'll probably be pretty late, though.
It's too dangerous, Ishimochi-san.
You shouldn't go outside,
even if it is in a car.
The rain and winds are too strong,
and we have no idea when it will stop.
I know, but I've got to
pick him up sooner or later.
Well then, maybe I'll just...
have Kyusho-kun spend the night here.
Huh?
No, it's perfectly fine!
Please don't worry about it.
All right. Goodbye.
Uh, I really shouldn't...
It's fine! Don't worry about it.
Here.
It's really okay! No need to worry.
I'll set it up so we can sleep
in separate rooms.
The second floor storage room
is empty right now, anyway.
O-Okay.
But you've already done so much...
I've got everything covered. Let's just
say the feeling is mutual, so it's fine.
I can't depend on Kyusho-kun all the time.
I gotta show him I'm dependable too!
Hmm?
But I wonder why the power
hasn't come back yet.
Yeah, it's been a while.
I don't feel great about leaving
that unfinished laundry overnight.
What should I do? Hand wash it after all?
Well, I guess it's finally back.
Kyusho-kun...
Yes?
I'm sorry, but I have to
get back to work right away!
Huh?
Feel free to relax
and make yourself at home.
There she goes again.
Start
Pause
These go here...
and these here.
Phew.
I think we're done.
Yeah.
Thank you so much for your help.
Sure thing.
We should be able to use the shower now,
so why don't you go on in first?
That'll give me a chance
to get your futon ready.
Oh. Thanks.
I'll have to check out
the backyard tomorrow.
Oh.
That tree went straight through
the roof over the porch.
Um, I'm out, so go ahead.
Kinme-san?
Oh, what?
Kyusho-kun...
I'm so sorry!
Um, would you mind if we slept
in the same room tonight?
But what about the other room?
Well, since I got to finish washing,
I'm using it to dry clothes right now.
I'm really so sorry!
If you don't want to,
I can sleep in the hallway.
No, I can't... make you do that...
But I mean, if it doesn't
bother you, I don't care.
Thank you!
Oh boy.
Then I'll go take a bath too.
Actually, last time I was in this room...
was the day that happened.
I'm sorry. Did I wake you?
No, it's okay. I was still awake.
Well, good night.
Good night.
There's still some rumbling
in the distance.
Sounds like it.
But if it's that far away,
I won't get scared, I think.
Just now in the bath,
I started wondering about what could
have caused me to be so afraid of thunder.
I wonder what started it.
Actually, I don't really know if
I've ever been to Hatsushima before.
The person I went with said it looked
like I was lost in my memories there.
Sometimes even recent memories,
memories from the last two years,
just up and disappear on me.
It's almost like somebody who isn't me
is doing things I'm not aware of
when I'm not looking.
But I don't think there's anything
I can do about that.
Kinme-san, if you ever forgot
about me and Kuriru and Moruda,
I think I'd...
Thank you! I know this was asking a lot.
No, it was fine! He even helped me out
a bunch around the shop.
Kyu was helpful for once?
Yes, he sure was!
Kyusho-kun, thank you for your help.
Well dang, Kyu! Nice job. Good for you!
Oh!
Kyusho-kun! Your bag, your bag!
Translation:
Editing and Typesetting:
Michael Arnold
Ashley Barboza
Quality Control:
Translation Check:
Riley Dalton
Sriram Gurunathan
Episode 10  A Top-Class Challenge!
Next time is "A Top-Class Challenge!"